http://www.espwaterproducts.com/privacy-policy/

Toggle navigation
Pages
Categories
FILTERS - LAMPS - PARTS
Ultraviolet (UV)
Reverse Osmosis (RO)
Learn RO
What Does a Reverse Osmosis System Remove?Understanding ROReverse Osmosis Buyer's GuideRO Technical Help
Learn UV
Understanding UVUV System Buyer's GuideBest UV Water Filters and UV Water Purifier ReviewsUV Technical Help
Learn General Water Information
Water Filtration SystemsWater Treatment & Filtration Frequently Asked QuestionsWater DictionaryWater Facts
BLOG
Loading... Please wait...
FILTERS - LAMPS - PARTS
Ultraviolet (UV)
Reverse Osmosis (RO)
Learn RO
What Does a Reverse Osmosis System Remove?Understanding ROReverse Osmosis Buyer's GuideRO Technical Help
Learn UV
Understanding UVUV System Buyer's GuideBest UV Water Filters and UV Water Purifier ReviewsUV Technical Help
Learn General Water Information
Water Filtration SystemsWater Treatment & Filtration Frequently Asked QuestionsWater DictionaryWater Facts
BLOG
HomeADDITIONAL RESOURCESPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer's internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.
SECTION 2 - CONSENT
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
How do I withdraw my consent?
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at customersupport@espwaterproducts.com or mailing us at: 1510 Randolph St. Ste 508, Carrollton, TX 75006
SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
SECTION 4 - BIGCOMMERCE
Our store is hosted on BigCommerce.com. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.
Your data is stored through Bigcommerce's data storage, databases and the general Bigcommerce application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.
Payment:
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Bigcommerce stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.
For more insight, you may also want to read BigCommerce's Terms of Service here or Privacy Statement.
SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
Once you leave our store's website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website.s Terms of Service.
Analytics
We use third-party web analytics companies, including Google, to collect information that will help us improve our site. We may use third-party advertising companies to help tailor site content to users or to serve ads on ESPWaterProducts' behalf. You may opt out of the aggregation and analysis of data collected about you on our website by Google Analytics by visiting https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and downloading and installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. You can also opt out of third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.
Links
When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
SECTION 6 - SECURITY
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.
SECTION 7 - COOKIES
Cookies or similar tools may be utilized on ESPWaterProducts.com as this technology allows us to provide you with tailored information relative to your interests when visiting our site.
What are cookies?
Cookies are small text files which a website may put on your computer or mobile device when you first visit a site or page. You can accept or decline "cookies" by setting your browser to notify you when you are about to receive a cookie. Cookies serve many functions including remembering your username and preferences, analyzing site performance, or helping us to provide you with relevant content. This information may also be used to improve our products and services or improve your overall experience on ESPWaterProducts.com.
This privacy policy outlines how ESPWaterProducts.com uses and protects information that you provide ESPWaterProducts.com when you use this site. ESPWaterProducts.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page
SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENT
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact customer service at customersupport@espwaterproducts.com.
Sign Up
For Exclusive Deals and Offers
Name
Email
Go to Home
Customer support and technical assistance is available at
877-377-9876  (M-F 8-5 CST)
